shoecarnival.com 2019-05-31

# Privacy Policy | Shoe Carnival | Shoe Carnival

PRIVACY STATEMENT

Your privacy is very important to us. This policy is intended to give you a clear understanding about Shoe Carnival, Inc. ("Shoe Carnival") practices regarding collection, use, and disclosure of information that you may provide online or in our stores. This Privacy Statement applies to the information collected at any of our stores, on our website, and through your membership in our SHOE PERKS Rewards Club Program. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using or submitting information online or in our stores.

About Children

This site is not intended for children under the age of 13. We will not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information via this site from visitors in this age group. We encourage parents to talk to their children about their use of the Internet and the information they disclose to web sites.

TYPES OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

1\. Passive Information Collected

As you navigate through this site, certain anonymous information can be passively collected (that is, gathered without your actively providing the information) using various technologies, such as cookies, Internet tags or web beacons, and navigational data collection (log files, server logs, clickstream). Your Internet browser automatically transmits to this site some of this anonymous information, such as the URL of the web site you just came from and the Internet Protocol (IP) address and the browser version your computer is currently using. This site may also collect anonymous information from your computer through cookies and Internet tags or web beacons. You may set your browser to notify you when a cookie is sent or to refuse cookies altogether, but certain features of this site may not work without cookies.

We use marketing consultants to help us maintain and analyze our data and allow us to market more efficiently. They may use cookies or web beacons to collect information about you, in connection with providing you information via email, Internet ads or direct mail about products and services that might be of interest to you. You can choose not to have this information used by our trusted third party advertising partners by contacting us to opt out.

2\. Personal Information You Provide

Shoe Carnival may ask you to submit personally identifiable information so that you can benefit from the specified features (such as online purchases, in-store purchases, order tracking, creating/updating a shoecarnival.com account, submitting a product review, joining the SHOE PERKS Rewards Program and resume submission) or to participate in a particular activity (such as sweepstakes, surveys or other promotions). You will be informed what information is required and what information is optional.

Categories of personal information you may provide include name, shipping address, billing address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, order information, SHOE PERKS Rewards Program member number, recipient's name and email address (if applicable). 

Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

Shoe Carnival may use information collected from you online and in stores to: 

  * process and deliver products you have ordered;
  * communicate changes in your order status; 
  * process your return or exchange;
  * customize the site to your preferences and tailor products marketed to you; 
  * respond to your inquiries;
  * provide information to SHOE PERKS Rewards Program members; and
  * collect and process your payments.

We offer gift cards for purchase. Information you provide to us to create a gift card is only used for that purpose, and is only disclosed to the person receiving the gift.

If you choose to create or update a shoecarnival.com account, you may save personal information in that account, to include name, shipping and billing addresses, and credit card information. This option is intended to streamline your shopping experience as it allows us to access your pre-saved information at checkout rather than entering the information for each online order.

Information We Share With Third Parties

Shoe Carnival uses third parties to support our business and provide services such as receiving, processing and fulfilling orders, encrypting credit card data as a further measure of securing the data, processing credit card payments, processing product reviews, technical support, and providing comparative performance information relative to our site. 

We may disclose the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us to third parties, but only:

(i) to contractors we use to support our business (such as fulfillment services, technical support, delivery services, affiliated partners and financial institutions), in which case we will require such third parties to agree to treat your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and use it for the same purposes;

(ii) in connection with the sale, assignment, merger or other transfer of the business of this site to which the information relates, in which case we will require any such buyer to agree to treat your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and use it for the same purposes; or

(iii) to respond to law enforcement requests or where required by applicable laws, court orders, or government regulations. 

If you choose to complete a product review, you will submit the review and the personal information that you choose to submit along with your review to a third party with whom we have contracted to accept, collect and manage the reviews. Any product review that you submit may be published by us on this website, in printed or television advertisements, or in emails. You may choose what, if any, personal information you elect to submit in your product review, such as your name or a nickname and location. The information you choose to submit as personal identification with your review may be published with your review in the manner described above.

Updating Personal Information and Opt-Out 

To keep personal information that you provide online or in stores accurate, current, and complete, please log-in to your shoecarnival.com account to update or modify your information, or contact us as specified below.

If at any point you would prefer to opt-out or reduce the frequency of promotional email, including email associated with SHOE PERKS Rewards Program, or mailings, please update your contact preferences on your shoecarnival.com account or follow the removal instructions in each message. 

Security

Shoe Carnival takes reasonable steps to protect personally identifiable information as you transmit it to our site and to protect such information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. You should keep in mind that no Internet transmission is ever completely secure or error-free. In particular, e-mail sent to or from this site may not be secure.

_Links to Other Sites:_ This site may contain links or references to other web sites to which this Privacy Policy does not apply. We encourage you to read the Privacy Policy of every web site you visit.

How to Contact Us

If you have any questions, comments, requests, or concerns related to this Privacy Policy or the information practices of this site, or if you would like to opt out of future communications, please feel free to contact us.

_Write Us:_

Shoe Carnival, Inc.  
Attn: Legal Department  
7500 East Columbia Street  
Evansville, IN 47715

 _Call Us:_

812.867.6471

 _E-Mail Us:_

info@shoecarnival.com

Updates to this Privacy Policy

As this Privacy Policy changes, the revised policy will be posted on this site. Please check back periodically, and especially before you provide any personally identifiable information

This Privacy Policy was last updated on August 8, 2011.
